让我们来谈谈将github上的内容与本地硬盘同步的不同方式
Let's talk about the different ways that we can synchronize what's on github with our local hard drive.
第一种方法是使用git clone命令。
The 1st way that we do this is by using a command called git clone.
Git克隆将获取GitHub存储库的副本并将其放在您的本地硬盘上。
Git clone will take the copy of the GitHub repository and place it on your local hard drive.
如果我们在本地硬盘上已经有了存储库的副本，
If we already have a copy of the repository on our local hard drive,
为了同步github上的信息，
in order to synchronize the information that is on github,
我们可以发出一个git fetch命令。
we can issue a git fetch command.
从远程存储库获取下载信息
Fetch downloads information from the remote repository
并将这些信息带到你的本地回购，这样它就会是最新的。
and brings that information to your local repo so that it's up to date.
现在，它实际上并没有对信息做任何事情，
Now, it doesn't actually do anything with the information,
但它确实会同步本地驱动器和远程驱动器之间的链接
but it does synchronize the link between what's on your local drive with what is on your remote
最后是pull命令。
Finally, there is the pull command.
Pull是一种获取的组合 还包括将远程存储库中的数据与本地版本合并
Pull is a combination of doing a fetch, but also merging the data that is in your remote repository with the local version.
让我们继续尝试这些不同的命令
So let's go ahead and try those different commands.
首先 我将尝试克隆一个存储库
1st off, I'm going to try to clone a repository.
要做到这一点，我们需要打开一个终端，
To do that, we're going to need to have a terminal open,
我要把它放在桌面上，
and I'm going to put this on the desktop,
那是我存放东西的地方，
which is where I've been storing things,
我需要发出一个Git clone命令，然后包含我想要克隆的文件的url。
and I need to issue a Git clone command and then include the url of the file that I want to clone.
为此，我们可以登陆网站，
For that, we can go to the website,
这里是一个按钮调用代码，你可以用它来下载链接。
and right here is a button call code that you can use to download the link.
点击这里 它会复制链接到仓库
So if I click right here, it'll copy the link to the repository.
现在，这个链接实际上只是存储库的url，加上扩展名.git，以防您忘记它。
Now, this link is really just the url of the repository, plus the extension .git, just in case you forget it.
一旦我们有了这个，我们就可以回到我们的终端粘贴我要点击回车。
So once we have that, we can go back into our terminal paste that you are all And I'm gonna hit return.
你可以看到它将所有内容下载到本地硬盘上
And you can see that it downloads everything into our local hard drive.
现在让我们回到桌面
Now let's go back into the desktop.
你可以看到它叫它，不管它叫什么，在github上。
You can see that it called it, whatever it's called, at github.
如果我们打开它，它会有所有在GitHub上的文件。
And if we open it up, it's going to have all the files that are on GitHub .
我们可以在Visual Studio Code中打开它，
And we could open this in something like Visual Studio Code,
但是我们已经把这个项目下载到桌面上了。
but we already have this project downloaded into our desktop.
在这个文件夹中 可以下载一个项目的多个副本
On this folder, it's okay to download multiple copies of a project.
你刚从GitHub下载的拷贝，
The copy that you've just downloaded from GitHub,
它实际上是git中存储的最新版本。
it's actually the latest version of what's stored in git of itself.
我们真的不需要这个，
We don't really need this,
我要把这个放到垃圾桶里，然后打开Visual Studio Code。
so I'm just going to put this on the trash, and I'm going to open Visual Studio Code.
我们应该有我们一直在做的项目
We should have the project that we've been working with here.
如果你看一下Visual Studio Code中的这一节，
If you take a look at this section in Visual Studio Code,
你会看到我们有主分支和固定的线分支，
you'll see that we have the main branch as well as to fix that line branch,
这个项目也不知道发生了什么，因为我们在GitHub上过时了。
and there's nothing really else that this project knows about what's happened to this project since we've outdated in GitHub.
所以我可以在这里发出一个git fetch命令，
So I can issue a git fetch command here,
它会负责查看GitHub上的数据并将其下载到当前项目中。
and it's gonna take care of looking at the data that's on GitHub and download it that into the current project.
如果你还记得的话，我们在github上创建了一个名为Title Change的分支
So if you remember, we created a branch on github called Title Change, a
所以它把那个分支带到了我们的本地存储库。
nd so it brought that branch into our local repository.
点击这里 可以看到这个分支也会出现在标题更改下
So if we click right here, we can see that this branch will also appear in here under title change.
注意它说它在origin/titlechange下
Notice that it says that it's under origin slash title change.
你可以看到这里有一些分支
So you can see that there are some branches up here.
这些是机器上的分支
These are the branches that are on this machines.
然后在github上有一些分支
And then there are some branches that are at Gitub.
这些都在原点下面，这是一个远端名称，
And those are under the origin, which is the remote name,
然后是分支的名称。
and then the name of the branch.
所以如果我们看一下我们的分支列表，
So if we took a look at our branch list,
我把它清除掉，然后执行一个git分支命令。
let me clear this out, and I'll do a git branch command.
你会看到它只向我展示了本地的两个分支，
You'll see that it's only showing me the two branches that are here locally,
但是我可以执行git branch -a命令。
but I can do a git branch -a command.
它会显示所有的分支 包括远程分支
That's going to show me all the branches, including the remote branches.
现在，如果我想检查其中一个分支，最简单的方法是，
Now, if I want to check out one of those branches, the easiest way,
如果你有Visual Studio Code，
if you have Visual Studio Code,
就是来到这里，点击任何你想从远程分支导入的分支。
is to just come over here and click on any of the branches that you want to bring in from the remote branch.
所以我可以点击这里，
So I could just click on this right here,
它会把我切换到标题更改分支，
and it's going to switch me over to that title change branch,
它会把它带到当地。
and it's going to bring it in locally.
你可以看到它已经在这里了
You can see that it's right here already.
我要切换回主分支，
I'm going to switch back over to the main branch,
我将发出最后一个命令，
and I'm going to issue the last command,
也就是git的pull命令，
which is the git pulll command,
这将会带来所有的变化。
that's going to try to bring in all the changes.
但是由于我创建这个存储库的方式，
But because of the way that I created this repository,
然后，我建立了一个从主分支到远程分支的上游链接。
I then set up an upstream link from my main branch to my remote branch.
所以我需要复制这个命令 然后粘贴
So I do need to copy this command right here, and I'll paste it.
我想做的是确保我与当地的分支机构联系起来，
And what I want to do is make sure that I tie in my local branch,
它被称为main，并链接到origin main。
which is called main, and link it to origin main.
这就是我需要执行的命令
So this is the command that I need to execute.
现在，main的本地版本已经下沉到main的远程版本。
Now, the local version of main has been sinked to the remote version of main.
让我们把这个弄清楚，并发出一个git pull。
Let's clear to this out and issue a git pull.
现在，所有在远程版本上的变化都在局部发生了变化，
Now, all the changes that were on the remote version of our sight have been changed locally,
如果我看一下索引，
so if I take a look at the index,
你会看到我确实更改了标题。
you'll be able to see that I do have that title change.
现在 我们要做的是
Now, what we want to do is
确保我们将新标题添加到列和媒体文件中
make sure that we add that new title into the columns as well as the media file.
所以我要到这里来，复制这个，
So I'm going to come over here and I'll copy this,
我将创建一个新的分支，
I'll go ahead and create a new branch,
只是为了向您展示git flow如何与远程存储库一起工作。
just to show you how git flow will work with a remote repository.
我们将执行git switch - c，然后我将这个命名为othertitlechanges。
So we will do a git switch minus c, and then I'll call this thing othertitlechanges.
这创建了一个新的分支，
This creates a new branch,
现在我可以进入其他文件，粘贴修改，
and now I can go into my other files, paste that change,
保存这个，粘贴修改，保存这个。
I'll save this, and paste that change, and I'll save this.
这些文件现在被修改了。
Those files are now modified.
我们把这个清除掉，我可以执行git add period和git commit，然后在这里放一条消息。
Let's clear this out, and I can do a git add period and git commit and put in a message right there.
现在我们回到main并合并其他titlechanges。
So now we'll go back into main and will merge othertitlechanges.
好了，现在我要做的是推送我所做的所有更改，
All right, so now what I want to do is push all of the changes that I've done,
幸运的是，将它们推送到GitHub上。
luckily, and push them onto GitHub.
我可以做git push它会推送我在本地做的更改，
So I can do a git push now that's gonna push the changes that I've made locally,
但只对主要的分支。
but only to the main branch.
你也可以用git push - - all，
So you can also do a git push minus minus all,
如果您想在所有分支中推送所有更改。
if you want to push all the changes in all the branches.
让我们来看看Github上发生了什么。
Let's take a look at what's happened on Github.
我要刷新一下这个页面，
I'm going to refresh this page,
你会注意到我更改了主分支中的所有内容
and you'll notice that I changed everything in the main branch
并将其他标题更改添加到我们的分支列表中。
as well as added this other title changes into our branch list.
现在，我可以只推othertitlechanges分支，然后创建一个拉取请求。
Now, I could have just push the othertitlechanges branch and then created a pull request.
这将工作 但变化是如此之小 我只是照顾它在主要分支以及
That will work, but the change was so little that I just took care of it in the main branch as well.
现在让我们来看看这个问题
So let's take a look at this issue Now.
接下来 我要结束这个项目
Next, I'm going to go to the project to sort of close this project out.
我会打开第一个版本。
I'll open up first release.
我要做的是把这个移到完成选项卡。
And what I'll do is move this over to the Done tab.
如果我想的话 我可以点击这里看看这里的问题
And if I want to, I can click on this right here and take a look at the issue over here.
所以这个问题可以直接从我的项目栏中解决，
So this issue can be closed directly from my project bar,
但在问题页上看更容易一些，我要发表评论。
but it's a little bit easier to see it all on the issues page, and I'm gonna make a comment.
我可以在这里输入签名，调出我项目中的名字列表，让特里知道。
And I can actually type in the atsign here to pull up a list of names in my project and let Terry will know.
特里会收到一条信息，是一封电子邮件，
Terry will get a message, which will be an email,
然后我会让特里知道改变已经发生了
and then I'll let Terry know that the changes happen made,
我将用这句话来结束这个问题。
and I'm going to close this issue with this comment.
现在我们有了我们在这里所做的一切的历史，
So now we've got a history of everything that we've done here,
一直到关闭这个问题，这意味着这个问题已经解决了。
all the way down to closing the issue, which means this issue has been fixed.
如果我们再回到项目，
If we go to projects again,
你可以看到这里的一切看起来都很好。
you can see that everything looks great here.
如果我想，我可以存档它，它会把它从待办事项列表中删除，
And if I want to, I can archive this, and it'll remove it from the list of to-dos,
这是你时不时想做的事。
which is something you want to do every now and then.
你也可以看到这个问题，
You can see that the issue also,
因为它很接近，所以它不再在这里的列表上。
since it's been close, it's no longer on the list here.
如果我想的话，我仍然可以通过封闭问题来找到它，
I can still find it if I want to by filtering by just closed issues,
或者其他我想听的方式
or in any other way that I want to hear.
对吧 最后我要做的就是为这个项目创建一个release
Right? So the final thing that I could do is create a release here for this project.
看起来现在还没有发布，
It looks like releases aren't showing right now,
你可以到这里，然后确保你打开了发布功能。
so you can go right here, and then make sure that you turn on the release feature.
所以发布就像是你网站的正式版本
So release is like an official version of your website.
你做发布的原因是你想让人们看到你视野的特定版本
The reason you do releases is because you want people to have access to a specific version of your sight.
你的存储库会一直在变化，
Your repository is going to change all the time,
你希望人们回到任何一个特定的版本，
and you want people to come back to any specific version,
所以如果他们在项目中使用它，
so that if they're using it on their project,
他们总是可以使用那个版本。
they can always have that version to work with.
现在我把它加回来了，
So now that I've added that back,
我可以创建一个新版本，然后给它一个版本。
I can go to create a new release, and I can give this thing a version.
当给它一个v1.0.0时，通常在网络上的版本有三个数字。
When give it a v1.0.0, usually versions on the web have three digits.
这是一个主版本。
This is a main release.
这是一个子版本，这是一个非常小的版本。
This is sort of a sub release, and this is a very minor release.
这有点像买来的修复
So this is sort of like bought fixes.
下一个是任何会破坏原始版本的变化，
And then the next one is any change that would break some things in the original release,
然后一个新的版本，比如第二个版本，将是一个全新的版本。
and then a new version, like a version two, would be a completely new version.
所以这个版本的目标将是发生在主分支中的任何东西
So the target of this release is going to be whatever happens to be in the main branch.
如果我想从这里开始，我可以选择其他分支，
I could choose some other branches if I want to from here,
然后我会给它一个发布标题，我就叫它first release。
and then I'm gonna give this the release title, and I'll just call it first release.
如果我想的话，我可以在这里写一些笔记，但我不需要这样做。
And I can write some notes in here if I want to, but I don't need to do that.
在这里你可以看到更多关于语义版本控制的信息。
And here you can see more information about semantic versioning here.
你也可以把它做成预发布版，
You can also make this a pre release,
这意味着你要让人们知道，这还没有准备好生产。
which means you're letting people know that this isn't production ready quite yet.
在这种情况下 你可以把它命名为v 1Alpha
In that case, you might name it something like this v .1 Alpha.
它真的不会被称为版本一
It really wouldn't be called a version one.
但是，如果你想这样做，
Or however, else you want to do this,
您可以在这里的语义版本控制中阅读这些注释。
you can read this notes over here in semantic versioning.
这不会是一个beta或类似的东西
This isn't going to be a beta or anything like that.
这将是一个正式的发布
It's going to be an official release.
有人说，发布发布。
Someone to say, publish release.
这给了你一个地方，你可以发布你所有的版本，
And this gives you a place where you can publish all your releases,
人们可以来这里下载你文件的源代码看看你的代码和状态。
and people can come in here and download the source code for your files and take a look at your code and that state.
这是人们可以经常去的地方
So that's something that people can always go to.
注意，它还为发布创建了一个小分支，
Notice that it also creates a little branch for the release,
这样，当你发布正式版本时，人们总是可以回到这个版本的代码。
and that way people can always come back into this version of the code when you made the official release.
你可以看到，github非常有用，不仅仅是创建不同版本的视觉。
You can see that github is pretty useful for doing more than just creating different versions of your sight.
所以除了拥有Git的时光机功能，
So in addition to having the capabilities of a time machine with Git,
Github真的给了你一种方法来创建一个社会环境，人们可以一起合作。
github really gives you a way to create a social environment where people can collaborate together.